<resources>
    <string name="app_name">REVIVER</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="home_screen">Home screen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="action">Action</string>
    <string name="tracker">Tracker</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="welcome_back_vishnu">Welcome Back, Vishnu</string>
    <string name="image">Image comes here</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="this_is_header_text">This is Header Text</string>
    <string name="this_is_description_text">This is Description Text</string>

    <string-array name="explore">
        <item>"The Medical Minute: 'Stop the Bleed' training saves lives"</item>
        <item>"GFES offers 'Stop The Bleed' training"</item>
        <item>"Learn how to ‘Stop the Bleed’ in trauma-related emergencies"</item>
        <item>"Comparison of two teaching methods for stopping the bleed: a"</item>
        <item>"KODE Medical Focus: Stop the Bleed"</item>
        <item>"Charlottesville Fire Department's Stop The Bleed training can"</item>
        <item>"From kitchen accidents to mass shootings, Stop The Bleed classes can show you how to save a life"</item>
        <item>"How to help someone with a gunshot wound"</item>
        <item>"YCFD provides additional training for 'bleed' program | News"</item>
        <item>"Stopping the bleed – what difference is it making to patient"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="description">
        <item>"The Medical Minute: 'Stop the Bleed' training saves lives. Applying the tourniquet to prevent bleeding during the first aid training indoors."</item>
        <item>"Great Falls Emergency services is well-equipped to help teach you how to "stop the bleed," also known as BCON training, which is short for"</item>
        <item>"Stop the Bleed kits also offer all the tools necessary to help someone in a life-threatening situation before the arrival of medical help."</item>
        <item>"After the teacher plays a video introducing Caesar and students have practised hands-on bleeding control skills, a scenario simulation is then"</item>
        <item>"KODE Medical Focus: Stop the Bleed KODE — We've all had to rush for a band-aid to deal with a cut finger or scraped knee. But sometimes the"</item>
        <item>"Charlottesville firefighters show members of the BUCK Squad how to stop severe bleeding and pack and dress wounds as part of Stop The Bleed"</item>
        <item>"Stop the Bleed training can be used in household accidents, like with a lawnmower or a snowblower, at car crash scenes, or with sports injuries"</item>
        <item>"It can take as little as five minutes for a person with a life-threatening injury to bleed to death. Much like CPR, basic bleeding control"</item>
        <item>"Last year, the Yuba City Fire Department rolled out its Stop the Bleed program as part of a nationwide campaign to better prepare the public"</item>
        <item>"Helicopter emergency medical services (HEMS) are expanding throughout the world, particularly in high-income countries,"</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>